Preliminary Inventory of the Carol Sklenicka Collection of Raymond Carver Materials, 1930s-2014, bulk 2000-2009 SPEC.RARE.0098
Ohio State University Libraries Special Collections
Carol Sklenicka Collection of Raymond Carver Materials
Bulk, 2000-2009
1930s-2014
SPEC.RARE.0098
Ohio State University Libraries Special Collections
24.5 Cubic feet
As of 2015, Carol Sklenicka is a biographer and essayist based in California. She is best known for her biography of Raymond Carver, "Raymond Carver: A Writer's Life," published in 2009.The Carol Sklenicka Collection of Raymond Carver Materials contains materials acquired by Carol Sklenicka while performing research for her biography of Raymond Carver, “Raymond Carver: A Writer's Life.” The collection materials date from the 1930s-2014, with the bulk of materials dating 2000-2009.
(20) cartons; (1) legal document box
Sklenicka, Carol, 1948-
Arrangement of Materials
The collection is unprocessed and is arranged in the order it was received. It is arranged alphabetically by topic in the first four boxes. Thereafter, materials are grouped by document type, such as legal, publishing, and interview transcripts, including related research notes.
Acquisitions Information
Donated by Carol Sklenicka, 2013 December
Access to Materials
Some materials in boxes 5 and 15 have restricted access and are not available for research until 2020. Materials in box 22 are restricted and may not be viewed without prior curatorial consent. The remainder of this collection is available for patron research, but may be used only in the Thompson Library Special Collections reading room.
Biographical Note
Carol Sklenicka is a biographer and essayist based in California as of 2015. She is best known for her biography of Raymond Carver, "Raymond Carver: A Writer's Life," published in 2009. It has been described as the first comprehensive work on Raymond Carver's life and writings.
Scope and Contents
The Carol Sklenicka Collection of Raymond Carver Materials contains articles, publisher drafts and edits, photo albums, legal documents and research notes related to Raymond Carver personally and professionally. The materials were acquired by Carol Sklenicka while doing research for a biography of Raymond Carver. The collection dates from the 1930s-2014, with the bulk of interview and other research notes from 2000-2009.
Carver, Raymond, 1938-1988; Sklenicka, Carol, 1948-; Authors, American--20th century--Biography; Authors, American--20th century--Correspondence; Photographs
- Abbott Dottie and Abbott Keith, undated (Box 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Carver files Abbott-Howell
- Adelman, Bob, 1987 (Box 1)
- Agents- Ray's, 1981-1984 (Box 1)
- Alcoholism, undated (Box 1)
- Altman, Robert, 1993 (Box 1)
- American Academy of the Arts The Strauss Award, 1983-1988, 2004 (Box 1)
- Arizona, undated (Box 1)
  Carver files Abbott- Howell
- Atlantic Monthly Press, 1981 (Box 1)
- Babcock, Bert (bookseller), 1983-1984, 2001 (Box 1)
- Banks, Russell, 2004 (Box 1)
- Beattie, Anne, undated (Box 1)
- Beginners, 2009-2010 (Box 1)
- Bellows, Saul, 1981 (Box 1)
- Benedict, Dianne, 1982 (Box 1)
- Bethea, Arthur on Poetry, undated (Box 1)
- Betz, Bruce and Matthew Barrows, 1984 (Box 1)
- Blades, John, 1978-1981 (Box 1)
- Blaise, Clark, 1965-1982 (Box 1)
- Bourjaily, Vance and Ting, 1977-1981, 2002-2003 (Box 1)
- Boyle, Tom, 2004 (Box 1)
- Brodkey, Harold, 1987 (Box 1)
- Busch, Fred, 1988 (Box 1)
- Busch, Marry Bucci (Syracuse), 2003 (Box 1)
- Buzbee, L., 1983 (Box 1)
- Carpeule, David (Saskatchewan), 1986-1995 (Box 1)
  Carver Files Abbott-Howell
- Carriveau, Jerry, undated (Box 1)
- Carruth, Hayden, 1979-1985 (Box 1)
- Carver, Christine La Rae, 2004 (Box 1)
- Carver, Ella, undated (Box 1)
- Carver, James, 2007-2009 (Box 1)
- Carver, Maryann, 1989, 2004, 2009 (Box 1)
- Carver, Maryann, 2003, 2006 (Box 1)
- Carver, Maryann Writings, 1998 (Box 1)
- Carver Notebook Pages, circa 1981 (Box 1)
- Carver, Vance, 2002-2005 (Box 1)
- Cecily, Diane, circa 2006 (Box 1)
- Cheever, John, 1984 October 23 (Box 1)
- Ciming, Michael, 1982-1983 (Box 1)
- Clallam County, Carver vs Gallagher, 1995 (Box 1)
- Collins Publishers, 1982-1983 (Box 1)
- Crawford, Max, 1978, 2002-2003 (Box 1)
- Crossland, Rich, 2008 (Box 1)
- Crumley, James, undated (Box 1)
- Davis, Jerry, undated (Box 1)
- Day, Dick, 1987-2003 (Box 1)
- Day, Dick Collection, 1963-1968 (Box 1)
- Dobyns, Stephen, 1995, 2009 (Box 1)
- Doherty, Tom, 1965-1989, 2005 (Box 1)
- Elkin, Stanley, 1984 Spring (Box 1)
- Erhart, Werner, est, 1987-2001 (Box 1)
- Esquire Inc, 1981-1983 (Box 1)
- Evenson, Brian, 2007 (Box 1)
- Facknitz, Mark, 1999 (Box 1)
- Fisketjon, Gary + Random House, 1981-1984, 2008 (Box 1)
- France- Carver Visit, 2004-2006 (Box 1)
- Fuller, Blair Squaw Valley Duffy's Alum, 1976-1983, 2002 (Box 1)
- Gallagher, undated (Box 1)
- Granta + Bill Buford, 1981 (Box 2)
  Carver Files Granta-Louria
- Gurganus, Allan, 2005 (Box 2)
- Gutterman, Leslie, 1978, 1984 (Box 2)
- Hall, Donald, 2005 (Box 2)
- Hall, James B., 2001, 2004 (Box 2)
- Halpern, Daniel | Antaeus/The Ecco Press, 1982-1987 (Box 2)
- Halpert, Sam, 1995 (Box 2)
- Hannah, Barry, 1982, 2010 (Box 2)
- Hansen, Ron, 1978-1979 (Box 2)
- Helprin, Mark, 2003 (Box 2)
- Henry, Dewitt Ploughshares, 1983-1987, 2003 (Box 2)
- Heynen, Jim, 2003 (Box 2)
- Hicks, Jack, 1998 (Box 2)
- Hills, Rust, 1982, 2003 (Box 2)
- Hitchcock, George, 1987, 2003 (Box 2)
- Hoagland, Tony, 2002 (Box 2)
- Houston, Jim, 1978-1983, 2001 (Box 2)
- Hribal, L. J., 2008 (Box 2)
- Hudson, Judy, 2007 (Box 2)
- Hugo, Richard, 1998 (Box 2)
- Howell, John M. and Gardener Joan/John P, 1982-1983, 2001 (Box 2)
  Carver Files Abbott- Howell
- Illness + Death of Raymond Carver, 2008 (Box 2)
- The Iowa Review, circa 1977 (Box 2)
- The University of Iowa, 1936-2002 (Box 2)
- Jackson, Jon A (email), 1970s (Box 2)
- Jarman, Mark, 2003 (Box 2)
- Jenks, Tom, 2001-2014, 2013 (Box 2)
- Johnson, Curt December Ed., 1965-2010 (Box 2)
- Justice, Jean (Don?), 2003-2004 (Box 2)
- Karr, Jay, 2003-2004 (Box 2)
- Kinder, Chuck, undated (Box 2)
- King, Jerry B., circa 2003 (Box 2)
- Kittredge, Bill, 1971, 1982, 2001 (Box 2)
- Koepf, Michael CA/MT "herbs", 2002 (Box 2)
- Kolbert, Dick, 1970s, 2002 (Box 2)
- Kryger, King, 2003 (Box 2)
- Lainsbury, G. P., undated (Box 2)
- Laurence + Carver Blind Man/Catch, 1970s, 2005 (Box 2)
- Leet, Majorie, 1983, 1993 (Box 2)
- 'Levee' Story by anonymous, 1966 (Box 2)
- Lish, undated (Box 22)
  Access to Materials
  Materials in this folder have restricted access and may not be viewed without prior curatorial consent.
  Carver Files Granta- Louria
- Lish, Gordon Paper Chase, 2001-2009 (Box 22)
- Lish to Carver Letters, 1979-1983 (Box 22)
- (DUPLICATE) Gallagher, T., 1982-2001 (Box 2)
- (DUPLICATE) Gardener, Len, 2002 (Box 2)
- Lish, Gordon, Esquire, Knopf, 1977-1988 (Box 22)
- (DUPLICATE) Gallagher Tess Correspondence, circa 2001 (Box 2)
- Raymond Carver Various Residencies, 1974-1978 (Box 10)
- Letters to Raymond Carver, 1965-1977 (Box 10)
- Reviews and Profiles of RC, undated (Box 10)
- Magazine Articles Written about Carver, 1963-1978 (Box 10)
- Lish-Johnson Correspondence, 1969 (Box 22)
- Lish- Carruth Correspondence, 1957-1966 (Box 22)
- Lish- Carruth II, undated (Box 22)
- Lish-Elkin Correspondence, 1965-1970 (Box 22)
- Lish Pre Esquire, 1965-1973 (Box 22)
- Looking for RC's birthplace, 1999 (Box 3)
- Louria, Mark, 2008 (Box 3)
- Lynn, George, 2002-2010 (Box 3)
  Carver files Lynn- Zigal
- Lynn, George Part II, 2004-2005 (Box 3)
  Separated Materials
- Marcus, Morton, 2000 (Box 3)
- Max D.T. article & etc., 1998 (Box 3)
- McCarriston, L, 2007 (Box 3)
- McClanahan, Ed, 2005 September (Box 3)
- McDonald, Herb, 1982 February 2 (Box 3)
- McGrath, Charles, 1980-1981 (Box 3)
- McGraw Hill Book Company Fred Hills, 1977-1981 (Box 3)
- McInerney, Jay, 1971-1989, 2007 (Box 3)
- McKeever, Jim, 1994-1995 (Box 3)
- Meschery, Joanne, 1981 (Box 3)
  Carver files Lynn-Zigal
- Meyers, Jeffrey, 1985 December 8 (Box 3)
- Mitchell, Adrian, 2003 (Box 3)
- Murakami, Yoko + Haruki, 1984, 2001 (Box 3)
- Murray, Bill, 1978, 1984 (Box 3)
- Myers, David G., 1996 (Box 3)
- Norman Gurney, 1977, 2005 (Box 3)
- Nova, Craig, undated (Box 3)
- O'Brien John, 1972-1989 (Box 3)
- O'Connor, Rob T. (Syracuse), 2003 (Box 3)
- Omak, undated (Box 3)
- OSU Archive, 1980, 2006 (Box 3)
- Pearce, Richard, undated (Box 3)
- Paul Don, 2005 (Box 3)
- Parkev, Thomas, undated (Box 3)
- Perspective + Thurston, 1960-1974 (Box 3)
- Phillips, Jane Anne, 1980 (Box 3)
- Photos & Maps, 1970s, 1980s (Box 3)
- Plumly, Stanely, 1982, 2003 (Box 3)
- Poems (notes), undated (Box 3)
- Pushcart Press, 1977-1984 (Box 3)
- Requests to which Raymond Carver replied, 1980-1984 (Box 3)
- Rodgers, Michael, 1982-1983, 2003-2004 (Box 3)
- Romon, Philippe, 2001-2003 (Box 3)
- Roth, Henry H., undated (Box 3)
- Ryan, Michael, circa 1982 (Box 3)
- Sacramento, 1998 (Box 3)
- Sadoff, Ira, 1981, 2001 (Box 4)
- Sanchez, Steph + Thomas, circa 2003 (Box 4)
- Schmitz, Dennis, 1998-2010 (Box 4)
- Shapiro, Alan, 2005 (Box 4)
- Simpson, Mona, 1982-1984 (Box 4)
- Sipper, Ralph SB Bookseller, 1995, 2001 (Box 4)
- Skenazy, Paul, 1989 (Box 4)
- Skyoles, John, 2004 (Box 4)
- Smith, Diane, 2003 (Box 4)
- SMU Festival, 1977, 1981 (Box 4)
- Solotaroff, Ted, 2005 (Box 4)
- Standiford, Les, 1997, 2000-2003 (Box 4)
- Stanton, Maura + Cecil, Richard, undated (Box 4)
- Sterling, John, 1977 (Box 4)
- Stone, Robert, undated (Box 4)
- Strand, Mark, undated (Box 4)
- Stull, William L., 1994, 2001, 2007 (Box 4)
- Swangers, Dave, 2000 (Box 4)
- Syracuse University, 1979-1984 (Box 4)
- Thurston, J., 1969 (Box 4)
- Tri Quarterly, 1980 (Box 4)
- Turow, Scott, 2002 (Box 4)
- Unger, Amy Burk, Circa 2003 (Box 4)
- Unger, Douglas, 2001-2009 (Box 4)
- Vaghn, Stephanie, 1981 (Box 4)
- Vause, Mikal, 1997 (Box 4)
- Vogan, Sara, 1981 (Box 4)
- Voight, Ellen, 1977 (Box 4)
- Wali, K + M, 2008 (Box 4)
- Ward, Robert, 1981, 2003 (Box 4)
  Carver file Lynn-Zigal
- Waters, Michael, circa 1980 (Box 4)
- Weigl, Bruce, 1982 (Box 4)
- Weissman, Judith, undated (Box 4)
- Welch, Jim, 1981, 2004 (Box 4)
- Williams, Joy, circa 2003 (Box 4)
- Wolff, Geoffrey, 1989, 2003-2008 (Box 4)
- Woodward, Kathleen, 1981, 2001 (Box 4)
- Yaddo with Curtis, 1976-1982, 2005 (Box 4)
- Yakima, 1985-2000 (Box 4)
- Yates, Richard, 2003 (Box 4)
- Young, Al, 2000 (Box 4)
- Young, Noel, 1979-1982 (Box 4)
- Young, Noel Capra Press, 1971-1983 (Box 4)
- Young, Tim, 2000-2002 (Box 4)
- Zigal, Tom, 2004-2008 (Box 4)
- "Our Raymond" Before Yaddo cut, 2008 April (Box 4)
  Carver bio edits December 2008- Spring 2009
- Short Stories in approximate order of composition, 2009 (Box 4)
- Carver bio with photos and index II, 2009 December 26 (Box 4)
- Scribner's Index, undated (Box 4)
- Carver bio with photos and index, 2009 July 24 (Box 4)
- Irina's Index, undated (Box 4)
- Email correspondence Carver and Carol, 2009 (Box 4)
- Deborah Morse edits to bio, 2008 (Box 4)
- Manuscript edits, undated (Box 4)
- Copy Edit 1st half, undated (Box 4)
- Copy Edit 2nd half, undated (Box 13)
- Manuscript FULL (831 pages), 2009 February 3 (Box 13)
- Raymond Carver's Various Residencies, 1967-1972 (Box 6)
- Raymond Carver's Various Residencies II, 1972-1976 (Box 6)
- Raymond Carver's Residency in Sacramento, 1960s (Box 6)
- Sylvia Kolbert San Francisco, 1980 (Box 18)
- Evelyn of Duncan's Mill + Richard Lourie, 1970s (Box 18)
- James Carver #2, 1996 October 23 (Box 18)
- Gary Thompson #1, 2001 July 20 (Box 18)
- Curt Johnson, 2002 February 25 (Box 18)
- Koepf, 2002 January 22 (Box 18)
- Diane Smith, 2003 January 23 (Box 18)
- Jack Hicks, 2002 October 2 (Box 18)
- Tracy Kidder, 2003 December 16 (Box 18)
- Maryann Carver, 2003 December 16 (Box 18)
- Ellen Bryant Voight, 2003 September 23 (Box 18)
- Curt Johnson|Colin Harrison, 2003 December 22 (Box 18)
- Marjorie Leet Ford, undated (Box 18)
- Carver Family Geneology, undated (Box 6)
- Carver Bibliography General Articles, undated (Box 7)
- Letters written by Carver II, 1982-1988 (Box 7)
- Letters written by Carver, 1978-1981 (Box 7)
- Magazine Publications, 1979-1988 (Box 7)
- 1st pass Carver edits, 2009 May 22 (Box 14)
- 2nd pass Carver edits, 2009 July 17 (Box 14)
- Raymond Carver manuscripts, circa 1980 (Box 14)
- Reviews of Raymond Carver, 1980-2001 (Box 14)
- OSU notes on Carver Collection, undated (Box 9)
- Bio draft and notes (extensive), undated (Box 9)
- Edits to Biography, undated (Box 11)
- Scribner edits, 2009 June 23 (Box 11)
- Edits to Bio (Extensive), 2009 (Box 11)
- Edits Harrison Colin, 2009 August 6 (Box 12)
- Simon and Schuster Edits, undated (Box 12)
- Scribner Edits, 2009 December 2 (Box 12)
- Colin Harrison Edits, undated (Box 12)
- Fickle, Chris + Estate, 1988-1989 (Box 5)
- MBC-CLC Suit ended for $5000 each, 1989-1990 (Box 5)
- Estate Reopened Amended Invent, 1990-1991 (Box 5)
- Summary of CLC's suit Renewal Rights, 1996 (Box 5)
- Rights for Short Stories, 1990 June 29 (Box 5)
- Altman, 1990 (Box 5)
- Renewal Rights, 1990, 1996 (Box 5)
- Altman Option, 1990 (Box 5)
- Q+A Tess, Calls to CLC, 1990 (Box 5)
- Interrogation of Tess, 1995 December 4 (Box 5)
- Lieberman, undated (Box 5)
- Renewal Rights Suit, 1996 (Box 5)
- Renewal Rights Cont'd., 1995-1996 (Box 5)
- Interrogation of Chris with answers, 1995 (Box 5)
- Pre 1978 Stories, 1996 (Box 5)
- Geyman Statement about damages, 1996 (Box 5)
- Raymond Carver A Writer's Life, 2009 February 3 (Box 5)
- Copy Edit 2nd half, undated (Box 5)
- Raymond Carver Critics Reviews, 1978-2001 (Box 14)
- Raymond Carver Written works, 1969-1987 (Box 14)
- Carver 2nd Pass edits, 2009 July-August (Box 14)
- Carver 1st Pass edits, 2009 May 22 (Box 14)
- Geyman statement about damages, 1996 (Box 15)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Cannot be viewed by public until 2020
- Mention of Ella's Illness, 1989 (Box 15)
- Reference to Supreme Court Case, 1990 (Box 15)
- Deposition of Chris, 1996 March 22 (Box 15)
- CLC Deposition- Assault Charge, 1996 March 22 (Box 15)
- McKeever, 1996 March 22 (Box 15)
- Deposition Cont'd and Clallam County Court Case, 1996 March 22, 1996 May 22 (Box 15)
- Deposition, 1990-1996 (Box 15)
- Claims against the estate, 1989-1996 (Box 15)
- ICM Commisions, 1989-1994 (Box 15)
- Court Case Cont'd., 1996 October 3 (Box 15)
- Last Will and Testament of Raymond C. Carver, 1988 August 9th (Box 15)
- Maryann's Deposition, 1989 May 4 (Box 15)
- Last Will and Testament of Raymond Carver, 1988 August 9th (Box 15)
- Value of the estate, 1988 August 9th (Box 15)
- Raymond Carver Estate, 1989 May 19 (Box 15)
  Cannot be viewed until 2020
- Vance's Removal as Plaintiff, 1989 June 7 (Box 15)
- More procedure, 1989 May 31 (Box 15)
- RC tax forms, 1982-1984 (Box 15)
- Defendant's Supplemental Memorandum, 1989 June 12 (Box 15)
- MBC Files against estate, 1988 December 3 (Box 15)
- Lawsuit MBC versus Tessa Gallagher, 1988-1989 (Box 15)
- Tessa Gallagher's replies, 1989 (Box 15)
- Arguments against kids + MBC, 1989 (Box 15)
- Affidavits, 1995 (Box 15)
- Tessa Gallagher, 1989-1995 (Box 15)
- Maryann Carver Declaration, 1995 September 25 (Box 15)
- McKeever Article Exhibit A, 1994-1996 (Box 15)
- Chris's Deposition, 1996 March 22 (Box 15)
- Protective Order Denied, 1996 February 22 (Box 15)
- Tess's Motion of Protection Order, 1995 September 25 (Box 15)
- Last Will and Testament of Raymond Carver, 1988 August 9 (Box 15)
- Christine Versus Tess, 1995 (Box 15)
- Protection Order Denied, 1995 October 20 (Box 15)
- Raymond Carver News Article, 1994 March 20 (Box 15)
- Altman, 1990 (Box 15)
- Palmer Institute of Authorship on Short Stories, 1952 (Box 15)
- Yakima Washington Info and Pictures, 1940s (Box 15)
- Research Materials, 2000s (Box 15)
- Ohio State stories, undated (Box 15)
- Artwork from Raymond Carver, undated (Box 15)
- Articles about Raymond Carver, undated (Box 15)
- Mail from Violet Archer, 2000 (Box 15)
- Palmer Institute of Authorship, 1953, 1956 (Box 15)
- Bankruptcy Papers, 1975 (Box 15)
- Bankruptcy, 1967 (Box 15)
- Carol Sklenicka Research Materials and Correspondence, 1950s-2010s (Box 16)
- Carver Bio Edits, 2008 April 23 (Box 17)
- Carver reading in Arcala, 1981 (Box 18)
- Carver at CSU Sacramento, 1987 February 26 (Box 18)
- Hitchcock, 2002 February 22 (Box 18)
- Schmitz- Sacramento, 2000 January 25 (Box 18)
- Hitchcock|Simon tape #2, 2002 February 22 (Box 18)
- Maryann Carver, 2003 August 10th (Box 18)
- Maryann Carver #2, 2003 August 10 (Box 18)
- Doug Unger tape #2, 2003 November 14 (Box 18)
- Doug Unger tape #3, 2003 November 4 (Box 18)
- Christine Carver, 2004 February 9 (Box 18)
- Robert C Downs, 2004 July 31 (Box 18)
- Carver, MB, 2005 December (Box 18)
- Maryann Carver, 2005 September 16 (Box 18)
- Carver #16 Don Archer Dick Day, undated (Box 18)
- Tobias Wolff, 2007 January 10 (Box 18)
- Curt Johnson, 2004 February 25 (Box 18)
- Craig Nova, 2006 December 18 (Box 18)
- Dobyns Stephen, 2006 November 4 (Box 18)
- Wolff Geoffrey Bath, Maine, 2006 November 3 (Box 18)
- Kinder and Cecily tape #2, 2002 Decmeber 2 (Box 18)
- John O'Brien #2, 2003 November 23 (Box 18)
- Sacto notes + Koepf, 2002 January (Box 18)
- A- Tony Hoagland, undated (Box 18)
- Dennis Covington, 2006 July 8 (Box 18)
- Sam Halpert, 2002 August 1 (Box 18)
- Neal Shinpaugh, 1998 March 29 (Box 18)
- Blair Fuller| Tomales, CA, 2002 July 10 (Box 18)
- Alice Ritchie|Burk Reed #21, 1998 July 17 (Box 18)
- John A Jackson #2, 2002 August 19 (Box 18)
- Franklin Casey, 2003 July 25 (Box 18)
- David Boxer, HSU Professor, 1997 July 17 (Box 18)
- Dick Day tape #3, 1997 July 17 (Box 18)
- Deborah Steele (Clatskanie editor), undated (Box 18)
- James and Lois Welch, 2002 August 18 (Box 18)
- Gutterman, Leslie, 2005 March 14 (Box 18)
- Minkoff Brothers, Paul Theiner, undated (Box 18)
- David and Lynn Swanger, 2000 October 16 (Box 18)
- Kinder and Cecily tape #1, 2002 December 2 (Box 18)
- Russell Banks: A TC Boyle:B, 2004 May 8, 2004 June 3 (Box 18)
- Ray Gonzalez, 2000 November 13 (Box 18)
- Richard S Kolbert, 2002 October 8 (Box 18)
- Marcus Mort, 2000 October 18 (Box 18)
- Robert O'Connor #1, 2003 July 20 (Box 18)
- John Skayles + Maria Flook, 2004 January (Box 18)
- Brendan Ward, 2006 April 28 (Box 18)
- Max Crawford #1, 2002 August 30 (Box 18)
- Christine Flavin|Norman Gurney, 2003 November, December (Box 18)
- Hannah Barry, 2004 October 4 (Box 18)
- Charles McGrath, 2006 April 28 (Box 18)
- Mary Karr|Charles Watson, 2003 November 12 (Box 18)
- Robert O'Connor #2, 2003 July (Box 18)
- Tom Zigal, 2004 September 10 (Box 18)
- Thomas Doherty, 2004 August 4 (Box 18)
- John Leggett, 2002 October 2 (Box 18)
- Hank Pieti, 2003 June 7 (Box 18)
- Bret Lott, 2006 May 30 (Box 18)
- Acan Shapiro, 2005 December 2 (Box 18)
- Bill Henderson, 2006 June 2 (Box 18)
- Edward Loomis: A|Lin Rollins:B, 2001 March 12, 2001 March 24 (Box 18)
- Hayden Carruth, 2003 November 12 (Box 18)
- Kinder and Cecily #3, 2002 December 8 (Box 18)
- Lee Byrd Pat Carr|El Paso, 2005 July (Box 18)
- Linda, McCarriston, 2006 November 14 (Box 18)
- Qais Al Awqati, 2006 May 12 (Box 18)
- John Sterling, 2006 October 11 (Box 18)
- Bruce Dobler, 2007 February 9 (Box 18)
- Richard and Lois Shelton|John Blades, 2003 November 7 (Box 18)
- Sally Daniels| Carol Lipson, 2003 November 10 (Box 18)
- Bob Shacochis, 2007 March 5 (Box 18)
- Mary Swander, 2003 December 3 (Box 18)
- Al Young #2, 2000 October 29 (Box 18)
- Marc Louria #2, 2001 June 20 (Box 18)
- Charlene Palmer|Ed MaClanahan, 2003 October 3, 2003 November 1 (Box 18)
- Hank Pieti, Yakima, 2000 July 17 (Box 18)
- Don Paul, 2005 January 17 (Box 18)
- Al Young #1, 2000 October 29 (Box 18)
- Jerry and Ruth King, 1997 September 19 (Box 18)
- Tom Jenks, 2004 May 3 (Box 18)
- Robert Pope, 2004 February 7 (Box 18)
- CJ Hribal, 2003 December 16 (Box 18)
- Shiloh; Waters; Moeller; Pope, 2004 January-February (Box 18)
- Oral notes on Yakima, 2000 July (Box 18)
- Bronson|Davis, 2002 September 16 (Box 18)
- Mary L Ford, 2003 September 2 (Box 18)
- Paul Shenazy, 2006 February 3 (Box 18)
- Pittsburgh (Kinder), 2006 April 13 (Box 18)
- Bill Kittredge|John O'Brien, 2003 October 4 (Box 18)
- Michael Waters|Jack Myers, 2004 March 26, 2004 June 1 (Box 18)
- Richard Day, 1997 July 16 (Box 18)
- Mark Jarman, 2003 July 16 (Box 18)
- Louria, 2001 June 20 (Box 18)
- Ken Ronsen, 2004 June 14 (Box 18)
- Bert Babcock, 2002 November 13 (Box 18)
- Jay McInerney #2, 2007 September 18 (Box 18)
- Jay McInerney #1, 2007 September 18 (Box 18)
- Jon A Jackson, 2002 August 19 (Box 18)
- Michael Rogers, 2003 July 18 (Box 18)
- Pat McGilligan on biography, undated (Box 19)
- Davis Family, 1995 October 5 (Box 19)
- Davis Family #2, 1995 October 5 (Box 19)
- Sandmeyer, 1995 October 6 (Box 19)
- Sandmeyer #2, 1995 October 6 (Box 19)
- King/Moeller, 1996 March 13 (Box 19)
- King/Moeller #2, 1996 March 13 (Box 19)
- Archer, 1996 March 14 (Box 19)
- Archer #2, 1996 March 15 (Box 19)
- Archer #3, 1996 March 15 (Box 19)
- Roy Hoover/Ada Hazen, 1996 April 25. 1996 June 13 (Box 19)
- King Kryger, 1996 June 27 (Box 19)
- Donaldson|James Carver, 1996 July 6, 1996 September 26 (Box 19)
- Leonard Gardner #2, 2002 October 11 (Box 19)
- Leonard Gardner #1, 2002 October 11 (Box 19)
- Liisa Erickson, James Carver, Lynn Stark, 2001 (Box 19)
- Don Halpern, 2004 September 27 (Box 19)
- Thomas Sanchez, 2005 January 23 (Box 19)
- Gary Thompson #2, 2001 July 20 (Box 19)
- James Crumley, 2002 August 15 (Box 19)
- Kennedy O'Connor, 2003 November 11 (Box 19)
- Gills, Dagoberto|Daniel Davis, 2004 September 13, 2004 September 17 (Box 19)
- Ted Solotaroff|Earl Cox, 2005 October-November (Box 19)
- Gallagher vs Sklenicka District Court, 2001 September 13 (Box 19)
- Norman Courney|Steve Salinger, undated (Box 19)
- Les Standiford, 2001 November 6 (Box 19)
- Hagen|Fred Hills, 2003 September 19 (Box 19)
- Video of Duffy Senior the Model for AA man in Where I'm Calling From, undated (Box 19)
- Carver Documentaries BBC Italian, undated (Box 19)
- Biography Chapters 1-30 + Photos, 2008 March 8 (Box 19)
- Goddard College Dorms, undated (Box 19)
- Kyve In Focus Carver, undated (Box 19)
- CDs and prints of Kate, Cecily, Saskatchewon, circa 1990 (Box 19)
- Photos: California, Negatives and Extras, 1990 (Box 19)
- Photos: Yakima, Negatives and Extras, 1997 September (Box 19)
- Photos: Ben Lomond, undated (Box 19)
- Photos: Raymond's Houses in Palo Alto and Cupertino, undated (Box 19)
- Photos: El Paso, 2005 July (Box 19)
- CD of photos to Carol from Maryann Carver, 2009 January 28 (Box 19)
- Slides of Yakima, undated (Box 19)
- Slides of NW Geography, undated (Box 19)
- Slides of Misc., undated (Box 19)
- CD: Robert Morgan Fischer "Follow a Hunch", 1995 (Box 19)
- Photo Album: California|Eureka, Arcata, Dick Day, Sacramento, Palo Alto, Santa Cruz, Cupertino, undated (Box 20)
- Photo Album: California|Chester, Chico, Nevado, undated (Box 20)
- Photo Album: Columbia River Gorge, 2000 (Box 20)
- Photo Album: Washington|Cascades, Yakima, undated (Box 20)
- Photo Album: Port Angeles, undated (Box 20)
- Photo Album: Raymond Carver's Lifetime, 1930s-1980s (Box 20)
- Photo Album:Washington|Yakima, Violet and Don Archer, undated (Box 20)
- Photo Album: Santa Barbara, Missoula, Syracuse, undated (Box 20)
- LIFE Magazine, 1981 April (Box 21)
- Carol's Map of El Paso, undated (Box 21)
- FireStarter7 on George Lynn, 2008 February (Box 21)
- Reader's Club Newsletter: Book Shop Santa Cruz, 2005 Summer (Box 21)
- Quarry, 1971-1972 Winter (Box 21)
- Quarry, 1972 Autumn (Box 21)
- Quarry Four, undated (Box 21)